{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ha.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786021409","data":{"timestamp":" 946786021409"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" dfe69bf6-4d5a-4dc8-8198-63b4b812befb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ha.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hata_hata-kosa-zamu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hata"," userResponse":" hata"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ha.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786031200","data":{"timestamp":" 946786031200"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" dfe69bf6-4d5a-4dc8-8198-63b4b812befb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ha.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hana_wale-ombe-hana"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hana"," userResponse":" hana"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ha.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786040444","data":{"timestamp":" 946786040444"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" dfe69bf6-4d5a-4dc8-8198-63b4b812befb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ha.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_haja_haja-ziwa-ndio"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" haja"," userResponse":" haja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ha.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786049386","data":{"timestamp":" 946786049386"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" dfe69bf6-4d5a-4dc8-8198-63b4b812befb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ha.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_haha_haha-yale-zamu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" haha"," userResponse":" haha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ha.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786057981","data":{"timestamp":" 946786057981"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" dfe69bf6-4d5a-4dc8-8198-63b4b812befb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ha.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_haki_haki-moto-damu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" haki"," userResponse":" haki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ha.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786067516","data":{"timestamp":" 946786067515"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" dfe69bf6-4d5a-4dc8-8198-63b4b812befb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ha.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_haki_haki-kike-kisa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" haki"," userResponse":" haki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ha.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786076812","data":{"timestamp":" 946786076812"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" dfe69bf6-4d5a-4dc8-8198-63b4b812befb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ha.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hana_hana-mpwa-damu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hana"," userResponse":" hana"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ha.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786085929","data":{"timestamp":" 946786085929"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" dfe69bf6-4d5a-4dc8-8198-63b4b812befb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ha.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_haja_watu-haja-zizi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" haja"," userResponse":" haja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ha.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786095430","data":{"timestamp":" 946786095430"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" dfe69bf6-4d5a-4dc8-8198-63b4b812befb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ha.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_haha_honi-haha-yadi"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" haha"," userResponse":" honi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ha.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786105954","data":{"timestamp":" 946786105954"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" dfe69bf6-4d5a-4dc8-8198-63b4b812befb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ha.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_haha_honi-haha-yadi"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" haha"," userResponse":" haha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ha.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786115114","data":{"timestamp":" 946786115114"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" dfe69bf6-4d5a-4dc8-8198-63b4b812befb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ha.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hapo_siyo-hapo-ziko"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hapo"," userResponse":" hapo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ha.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786120892","data":{"timestamp":" 946786120890"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" dfe69bf6-4d5a-4dc8-8198-63b4b812befb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ha.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_hapo_siyo-hapo-ziko"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786138162","data":{"timestamp":" 946786138161"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" a8814e04-fe9b-477d-98af-409ac6553ed5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kusoma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786139088","data":{"timestamp":" 946786139087"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" a8814e04-fe9b-477d-98af-409ac6553ed5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kusoma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAPENDA"," userResponse":" NINAPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786139943","data":{"timestamp":" 946786139942"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" a8814e04-fe9b-477d-98af-409ac6553ed5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kusoma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786145026","data":{"timestamp":" 946786145025"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" a8814e04-fe9b-477d-98af-409ac6553ed5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kusoma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786165387","data":{"timestamp":" 946786165387"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" a8814e04-fe9b-477d-98af-409ac6553ed5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kusoma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAPENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786172460","data":{"timestamp":" 946786172459"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" a8814e04-fe9b-477d-98af-409ac6553ed5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kusoma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786175502","data":{"timestamp":" 946786175501"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" a8814e04-fe9b-477d-98af-409ac6553ed5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitamsomea nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAMSOMEA"," userResponse":" NITAMSOMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786176460","data":{"timestamp":" 946786176459"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" a8814e04-fe9b-477d-98af-409ac6553ed5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitamsomea nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786180536","data":{"timestamp":" 946786180535"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" a8814e04-fe9b-477d-98af-409ac6553ed5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitamsomea nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NITAMSOMEA"," userResponse":" START_NITAMSOMEA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786181725","data":{"timestamp":" 946786181724"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" a8814e04-fe9b-477d-98af-409ac6553ed5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitamsomea nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NITAMSOMEA"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786183606","data":{"timestamp":" 946786183605"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" a8814e04-fe9b-477d-98af-409ac6553ed5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitamsomea nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAMSOMEA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786187217","data":{"timestamp":" 946786187217"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" a8814e04-fe9b-477d-98af-409ac6553ed5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitamsomea nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786189822","data":{"timestamp":" 946786189821"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" a8814e04-fe9b-477d-98af-409ac6553ed5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lesiba amelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LESIBA"," userResponse":" LESIBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786190839","data":{"timestamp":" 946786190838"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" a8814e04-fe9b-477d-98af-409ac6553ed5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lesiba amelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMELALA"," userResponse":" AMELALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786193613","data":{"timestamp":" 946786193613"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" a8814e04-fe9b-477d-98af-409ac6553ed5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lesiba amelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LESIBA"," userResponse":" LESIBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786197147","data":{"timestamp":" 946786197147"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" a8814e04-fe9b-477d-98af-409ac6553ed5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lesiba amelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMELALA"," userResponse":" AMELALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786200171","data":{"timestamp":" 946786200171"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" a8814e04-fe9b-477d-98af-409ac6553ed5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitamsomea nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAMSOMEA"," userResponse":" NITAMSOMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786201131","data":{"timestamp":" 946786201130"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" a8814e04-fe9b-477d-98af-409ac6553ed5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitamsomea nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786203621","data":{"timestamp":" 946786203621"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" a8814e04-fe9b-477d-98af-409ac6553ed5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitamsomea nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NITAMSOMEA"," userResponse":" START_NITAMSOMEA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786204742","data":{"timestamp":" 946786204742"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" a8814e04-fe9b-477d-98af-409ac6553ed5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitamsomea nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAMSOMEA"," userResponse":" NITAMSOMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786205260","data":{"timestamp":" 946786205259"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" a8814e04-fe9b-477d-98af-409ac6553ed5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitamsomea nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786207523","data":{"timestamp":" 946786207522"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" a8814e04-fe9b-477d-98af-409ac6553ed5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama na bibi wanapika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786207756","data":{"timestamp":" 946786207755"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" a8814e04-fe9b-477d-98af-409ac6553ed5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama na bibi wanapika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786208301","data":{"timestamp":" 946786208300"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" a8814e04-fe9b-477d-98af-409ac6553ed5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama na bibi wanapika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BIBI"," userResponse":" BIBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786209337","data":{"timestamp":" 946786209336"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" a8814e04-fe9b-477d-98af-409ac6553ed5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama na bibi wanapika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAPIKA"," userResponse":" WANAPIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786211323","data":{"timestamp":" 946786211322"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" a8814e04-fe9b-477d-98af-409ac6553ed5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama na bibi wanapika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786211637","data":{"timestamp":" 946786211636"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" a8814e04-fe9b-477d-98af-409ac6553ed5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama na bibi wanapika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786212022","data":{"timestamp":" 946786212021"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" a8814e04-fe9b-477d-98af-409ac6553ed5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama na bibi wanapika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BIBI"," userResponse":" BIBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786213046","data":{"timestamp":" 946786213046"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" a8814e04-fe9b-477d-98af-409ac6553ed5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama na bibi wanapika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAPIKA"," userResponse":" WANAPIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786215347","data":{"timestamp":" 946786215346"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" a8814e04-fe9b-477d-98af-409ac6553ed5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani nitamsomea?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786216924","data":{"timestamp":" 946786216923"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" a8814e04-fe9b-477d-98af-409ac6553ed5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani nitamsomea?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAMSOMEA"," userResponse":" NITAMSOMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786218791","data":{"timestamp":" 946786218791"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" a8814e04-fe9b-477d-98af-409ac6553ed5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani nitamsomea?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786219289","data":{"timestamp":" 946786219288"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" a8814e04-fe9b-477d-98af-409ac6553ed5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani nitamsomea?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NITAMSOMEA"," userResponse":" START_NITAMSOMEA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786225136","data":{"timestamp":" 946786225136"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" a8814e04-fe9b-477d-98af-409ac6553ed5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani nitamsomea?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NITAMSOMEA"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786226996","data":{"timestamp":" 946786226995"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" a8814e04-fe9b-477d-98af-409ac6553ed5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani nitamsomea?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAMSOMEA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786230020","data":{"timestamp":" 946786230019"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" a8814e04-fe9b-477d-98af-409ac6553ed5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitamsomea nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAMSOMEA"," userResponse":" NITAMSOMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786230202","data":{"timestamp":" 946786230202"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" a8814e04-fe9b-477d-98af-409ac6553ed5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitamsomea nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786234694","data":{"timestamp":" 946786234693"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" a8814e04-fe9b-477d-98af-409ac6553ed5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitamsomea nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NITAMSOMEA"," userResponse":" START_NITAMSOMEA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786238088","data":{"timestamp":" 946786238087"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" a8814e04-fe9b-477d-98af-409ac6553ed5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitamsomea nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NITAMSOMEA"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786239970","data":{"timestamp":" 946786239969"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" a8814e04-fe9b-477d-98af-409ac6553ed5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitamsomea nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAMSOMEA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786242959","data":{"timestamp":" 946786242958"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" a8814e04-fe9b-477d-98af-409ac6553ed5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitamsomea nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786244868","data":{"timestamp":" 946786244868"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" a8814e04-fe9b-477d-98af-409ac6553ed5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi mwenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAWEZA"," userResponse":" NAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786245939","data":{"timestamp":" 946786245938"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" a8814e04-fe9b-477d-98af-409ac6553ed5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi mwenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTULIA"," userResponse":" KUTULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786246194","data":{"timestamp":" 946786246194"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" a8814e04-fe9b-477d-98af-409ac6553ed5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi mwenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786247608","data":{"timestamp":" 946786247607"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" a8814e04-fe9b-477d-98af-409ac6553ed5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi mwenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKIFURAHIA"," userResponse":" KUKIFURAHIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786248338","data":{"timestamp":" 946786248337"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" a8814e04-fe9b-477d-98af-409ac6553ed5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi mwenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITABU"," userResponse":" KITABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786248980","data":{"timestamp":" 946786248979"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" a8814e04-fe9b-477d-98af-409ac6553ed5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi mwenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786249798","data":{"timestamp":" 946786249798"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" a8814e04-fe9b-477d-98af-409ac6553ed5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi mwenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYEWE"," userResponse":" MWENYEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786258276","data":{"timestamp":" 946786258275"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" a8814e04-fe9b-477d-98af-409ac6553ed5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi mwenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAWEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786265166","data":{"timestamp":" 946786265166"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" a8814e04-fe9b-477d-98af-409ac6553ed5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi mwenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTULIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786271415","data":{"timestamp":" 946786271414"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" a8814e04-fe9b-477d-98af-409ac6553ed5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi mwenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786277628","data":{"timestamp":" 946786277628"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" a8814e04-fe9b-477d-98af-409ac6553ed5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi mwenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKIFURAHIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786283617","data":{"timestamp":" 946786283617"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" a8814e04-fe9b-477d-98af-409ac6553ed5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi mwenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITABU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786289729","data":{"timestamp":" 946786289727"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" a8814e04-fe9b-477d-98af-409ac6553ed5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi mwenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786295722","data":{"timestamp":" 946786295722"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" a8814e04-fe9b-477d-98af-409ac6553ed5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi mwenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYEWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786297763","data":{"timestamp":" 946786297762"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" a8814e04-fe9b-477d-98af-409ac6553ed5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi mwenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786297991","data":{"timestamp":" 946786297991"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" a8814e04-fe9b-477d-98af-409ac6553ed5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi mwenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYEWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786315478","data":{"timestamp":" 946786315478"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" 48678f4f-0781-4750-a2f5-c0a2a1c2a150"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kusoma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786315860","data":{"timestamp":" 946786315859"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" 48678f4f-0781-4750-a2f5-c0a2a1c2a150"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kusoma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAPENDA"," userResponse":" NINAPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786315998","data":{"timestamp":" 946786315997"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" 48678f4f-0781-4750-a2f5-c0a2a1c2a150"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kusoma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786317697","data":{"timestamp":" 946786317697"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" 48678f4f-0781-4750-a2f5-c0a2a1c2a150"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kusoma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786318623","data":{"timestamp":" 946786318623"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" 48678f4f-0781-4750-a2f5-c0a2a1c2a150"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kusoma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAPENDA"," userResponse":" NINAPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786319480","data":{"timestamp":" 946786319479"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" 48678f4f-0781-4750-a2f5-c0a2a1c2a150"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kusoma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786323868","data":{"timestamp":" 946786323867"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" 48678f4f-0781-4750-a2f5-c0a2a1c2a150"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitamsomea nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NITAMSOMEA"," userResponse":" START_NITAMSOMEA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786325200","data":{"timestamp":" 946786325200"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" 48678f4f-0781-4750-a2f5-c0a2a1c2a150"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitamsomea nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAMSOMEA"," userResponse":" NITAMSOMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786331505","data":{"timestamp":" 946786331504"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" 48678f4f-0781-4750-a2f5-c0a2a1c2a150"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitamsomea nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" START_NITAMSOMEA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786332752","data":{"timestamp":" 946786332751"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" 48678f4f-0781-4750-a2f5-c0a2a1c2a150"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitamsomea nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786335217","data":{"timestamp":" 946786335216"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" 48678f4f-0781-4750-a2f5-c0a2a1c2a150"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitamsomea nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAMSOMEA"," userResponse":" NITAMSOMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786336170","data":{"timestamp":" 946786336169"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" 48678f4f-0781-4750-a2f5-c0a2a1c2a150"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitamsomea nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786341283","data":{"timestamp":" 946786341282"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" 48678f4f-0781-4750-a2f5-c0a2a1c2a150"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lesiba amelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LESIBA"," userResponse":" LESIBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786342086","data":{"timestamp":" 946786342085"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" 48678f4f-0781-4750-a2f5-c0a2a1c2a150"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lesiba amelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMELALA"," userResponse":" AMELALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786344120","data":{"timestamp":" 946786344119"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" 48678f4f-0781-4750-a2f5-c0a2a1c2a150"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lesiba amelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LESIBA"," userResponse":" LESIBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786345135","data":{"timestamp":" 946786345134"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" 48678f4f-0781-4750-a2f5-c0a2a1c2a150"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lesiba amelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMELALA"," userResponse":" AMELALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786349600","data":{"timestamp":" 946786349599"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" 48678f4f-0781-4750-a2f5-c0a2a1c2a150"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitamsomea nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NITAMSOMEA"," userResponse":" START_NITAMSOMEA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786351027","data":{"timestamp":" 946786351026"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" 48678f4f-0781-4750-a2f5-c0a2a1c2a150"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitamsomea nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NITAMSOMEA"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786352879","data":{"timestamp":" 946786352878"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" 48678f4f-0781-4750-a2f5-c0a2a1c2a150"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitamsomea nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAMSOMEA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786359852","data":{"timestamp":" 946786359852"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" 48678f4f-0781-4750-a2f5-c0a2a1c2a150"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitamsomea nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" START_NITAMSOMEA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786360913","data":{"timestamp":" 946786360913"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" 48678f4f-0781-4750-a2f5-c0a2a1c2a150"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitamsomea nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786363389","data":{"timestamp":" 946786363388"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" 48678f4f-0781-4750-a2f5-c0a2a1c2a150"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitamsomea nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAMSOMEA"," userResponse":" NITAMSOMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786364344","data":{"timestamp":" 946786364343"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" 48678f4f-0781-4750-a2f5-c0a2a1c2a150"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitamsomea nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786369029","data":{"timestamp":" 946786369029"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" 48678f4f-0781-4750-a2f5-c0a2a1c2a150"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama na bibi wanapika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786369199","data":{"timestamp":" 946786369199"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" 48678f4f-0781-4750-a2f5-c0a2a1c2a150"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama na bibi wanapika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786369621","data":{"timestamp":" 946786369621"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" 48678f4f-0781-4750-a2f5-c0a2a1c2a150"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama na bibi wanapika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BIBI"," userResponse":" BIBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786370735","data":{"timestamp":" 946786370734"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" 48678f4f-0781-4750-a2f5-c0a2a1c2a150"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama na bibi wanapika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAPIKA"," userResponse":" WANAPIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786372398","data":{"timestamp":" 946786372398"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" 48678f4f-0781-4750-a2f5-c0a2a1c2a150"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama na bibi wanapika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786372630","data":{"timestamp":" 946786372629"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" 48678f4f-0781-4750-a2f5-c0a2a1c2a150"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama na bibi wanapika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786373176","data":{"timestamp":" 946786373175"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" 48678f4f-0781-4750-a2f5-c0a2a1c2a150"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama na bibi wanapika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BIBI"," userResponse":" BIBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786374212","data":{"timestamp":" 946786374212"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" 48678f4f-0781-4750-a2f5-c0a2a1c2a150"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama na bibi wanapika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAPIKA"," userResponse":" WANAPIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786378488","data":{"timestamp":" 946786378488"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" 48678f4f-0781-4750-a2f5-c0a2a1c2a150"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani nitamsomea?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786379029","data":{"timestamp":" 946786379029"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" 48678f4f-0781-4750-a2f5-c0a2a1c2a150"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani nitamsomea?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NITAMSOMEA"," userResponse":" START_NITAMSOMEA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786386478","data":{"timestamp":" 946786386477"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" 48678f4f-0781-4750-a2f5-c0a2a1c2a150"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani nitamsomea?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NITAMSOMEA"," userResponse":" START_NITAMSOMEA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786388331","data":{"timestamp":" 946786388330"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" 48678f4f-0781-4750-a2f5-c0a2a1c2a150"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani nitamsomea?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAMSOMEA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786390102","data":{"timestamp":" 946786390101"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" 48678f4f-0781-4750-a2f5-c0a2a1c2a150"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani nitamsomea?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786391675","data":{"timestamp":" 946786391674"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" 48678f4f-0781-4750-a2f5-c0a2a1c2a150"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani nitamsomea?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAMSOMEA"," userResponse":" NITAMSOMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786396034","data":{"timestamp":" 946786396034"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" 48678f4f-0781-4750-a2f5-c0a2a1c2a150"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba na mjomba wanarekebisha gari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786396329","data":{"timestamp":" 946786396329"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" 48678f4f-0781-4750-a2f5-c0a2a1c2a150"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba na mjomba wanarekebisha gari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786396728","data":{"timestamp":" 946786396727"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" 48678f4f-0781-4750-a2f5-c0a2a1c2a150"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba na mjomba wanarekebisha gari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MJOMBA"," userResponse":" START_MJOMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786404745","data":{"timestamp":" 946786404744"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" 48678f4f-0781-4750-a2f5-c0a2a1c2a150"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba na mjomba wanarekebisha gari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJOMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786414813","data":{"timestamp":" 946786414813"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" 48678f4f-0781-4750-a2f5-c0a2a1c2a150"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba na mjomba wanarekebisha gari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAREKEBISHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786421061","data":{"timestamp":" 946786421060"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" 48678f4f-0781-4750-a2f5-c0a2a1c2a150"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba na mjomba wanarekebisha gari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786422716","data":{"timestamp":" 946786422715"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" 48678f4f-0781-4750-a2f5-c0a2a1c2a150"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba na mjomba wanarekebisha gari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786423023","data":{"timestamp":" 946786423022"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" 48678f4f-0781-4750-a2f5-c0a2a1c2a150"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba na mjomba wanarekebisha gari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786423750","data":{"timestamp":" 946786423749"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" 48678f4f-0781-4750-a2f5-c0a2a1c2a150"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba na mjomba wanarekebisha gari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJOMBA"," userResponse":" MJOMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786425060","data":{"timestamp":" 946786425060"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" 48678f4f-0781-4750-a2f5-c0a2a1c2a150"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba na mjomba wanarekebisha gari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAREKEBISHA"," userResponse":" WANAREKEBISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786425778","data":{"timestamp":" 946786425777"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" 48678f4f-0781-4750-a2f5-c0a2a1c2a150"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba na mjomba wanarekebisha gari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786430244","data":{"timestamp":" 946786430244"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" 48678f4f-0781-4750-a2f5-c0a2a1c2a150"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitamsomea nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NITAMSOMEA"," userResponse":" START_NITAMSOMEA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786437626","data":{"timestamp":" 946786437626"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" 48678f4f-0781-4750-a2f5-c0a2a1c2a150"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Nitamsomea nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786437770","data":{"timestamp":" 946786437770"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_070630"," gameId":" 48678f4f-0781-4750-a2f5-c0a2a1c2a150"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitamsomea nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NITAMSOMEA"," userResponse":" START_NITAMSOMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}